

Contact

- thanhtikezaw-dev.vercel.app
- +959-762695080
- yukihirasouma741@gmail.com
- Yangon, Myanmar

Skills

- MERN stack
- Reactjs, Nextjs
- Html, Css, Javascript
- Python
- Nodejs
- git, github
- UI/UX design

Language

English

Upperintermediate

Japanese

Progressing N2

Than Htike Zaw

Frontend Developer

I was an engineering student from MTU. I didn't graduate due to COVID-19 and political issues in my country, so I had to quit in my final year (finished my thesis and about 2 months left till graduate). However, I gained a lot of experience through various projects and internships related to my field, and I have a good understanding of teamwork and soft skills such as communication. I am now working as a full-stack developer, which is something I am passionate about.

Education

Mandalay Technological University (MTU-MIT)

Mechanical Engineering

2014--2020

- Learnt fundamental engineering sense and theories, designing machine parts, logical thinking
- Learnt team-work skills, communication skills, management skills through with many projects

CS50 -Computer Science on Edx

Web development

2021-2022

· Learnt data structures, algorithms and logical thinking

Experience

Automotive Engineer (internship)

2018-2020

United Eleven, Suzuki Mandalay

Capital Automotive Yangon (Ford, Jaguar)

Japanese Instructor (full-time)

2021-2022

Taught N5 and N4 levels through online platform

Graphic Designer(part-time)

2021-2022

responsible for graphic design for advertiment of delivery company on facebook

Web developer (freelance)

2022-present

Frontend Development for websites using Reactjs and Nextjs.